Guide to the San Francisco Bay Task Force World Cup Soccer Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
San Francisco Bay Task Force World Cup Soccer records
1990-2011
SC1161
San Francisco Bay Task Force 1994
1.5 Linear feet
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Access Terms
Liecty, Derek; Soccer.; World Cup (Soccer)--United States.
Collection Contents
- Records, 1990-2011
  - Task Force '94 (1 of 4), 1990-1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Contains bylaws and resolutions sections
  - Task Force '94 (2 of 4), 1990-1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Contains directories and correspondence sections
  - Task Force '94 (3 of 4), 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Contains minutes (1 of 2) section
  - Task Force '94 (4 of 4), 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Contains minutes (2 of 2) section
  - Soccer Legacy (1 of 4), 1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Contains grants section
  - Soccer Legacy (2 of 4), 1995-2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Contains applications section
  - Soccer Legacy (3 of 4), 2001-2011 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Contains tech soup software, web site, and Bay Area scores sections
  - Soccer Legacy (4 of 4), 2004-2010 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Contains directors/officers insurance section
  - Soccer Legacy Finance Tax Returns (1 of 2), 1995-2010 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Contains fundraising, finance, and tax returns sections
  - Soccer Legacy Finance Tax Returns (2 of 2), 1995-2004 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Soccer Legacy Articles Bylaws Minutes, 1995-2008 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Contains bylaws/articles, directory, meetings/minutes, to do, hotel, daily schedule, meals, entertainment, competition, and CONCACAF sections
  - Soccer Legacy Correspondence, 1995-2005 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - SF Bay Task Force '94 Tax Exempt Status Finances, 1991-2002 (Box 1, Folder 13)